Something magical is about to unfold in the most unexpected place.
The Pallbearer is a comedy, romance film directed by Matt Reeves.
Aspiring architect Tom Thompson is told by mysterious Ruth Abernathy
that his best friend, "Bill," has taken his own life.
Except that Tom has never met Bill and neither have his incredulous friends.
So when Tom foolishly agrees to give the eulogy at Bill's funeral, it sets him on a collision course with Ruth -- who is
revealed to be Bill's oversexed mother -- and Julie DeMarco, the longtime crush Tom hasn't seen since they were teens.
Tom Thompson, played by David Schwimmer.
Julie DeMarco, played by Gwyneth Paltrow.
Brad Schorr, played by Michael Rapaport.
Cynthia, played by Toni Collette.
Tom's Mother, played by Carol Kane.
Scott, played by Michael Vartan.
The Pallbearer is a 1996 American romantic comedy film co-written and directed by Matt Reeves in his directorial debut and
starring David Schwimmer, Gwyneth Paltrow, Toni Collette, Michael Vartan, Michael Rapaport, and Barbara Hershey.
It was screened in the Un Certain Regard section
at the 1996 Cannes Film Festival.
and received unfavorable reviews.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.